Whether it is to produce complex costume effects or to pursue the details of the display,
I believe that everyone can get the knowledge they want from the sharing just now.
Since we are talking about the details,
it is not just the software that will help everyone to continuously evolve the works.
The hardware equipment also needs to meet our creative needs.
Mingji's professional design display is developed and launched for the needs of all kinds of designers.
Next, let's welcome the channel manager of Mingji Shanghai, Mr. Tan Yachuan,
to introduce the Mingji professional display.
Thank you.
Good afternoon, everyone.
I am the channel manager of the Mingji professional design display.
Today, I will share with you the contents of the Mingji PD series professional design display.
First of all, the first question is,
why are we here?
This is the MD user interface.
Why are we here?
Actually, our PD and MD have the same purpose.
MD is a marvelous designer.
Our PD is a professional designer.
We are all a brand built for professional designers.
The Mingji PD series professional design display
is based on the professional display of Mingji for more than 20 years.
We have the experience of professional design display.
Since 2013,
we have been divided into the field of design display.
We have been trying to create a high-efficiency tool for our designers.
Since we have been focused on the display of the screen,
we have also entered the industry,
organizing and participating in some industry forums,
and even leading the development of the industry.
We hope to create a platform for professional designers
to show their ideas and express themselves.
We also want to promote the transformation from China to China.
This is also one of our questions.
Let's go back to our product list.
For most designers,
the display is a tool that designers have frequent contact with.
It is also the most important display device.
Next, I will show you through a short video
how the display interacts with our daily work and daily life.
How does Mingji help you through the display?
What kind of display does a designer need?
For a designer,
if the color is not accurate,
the effort is in vain.
In the eyes of ordinary people,
a single black and white gray
may be like a hundred kinds of black and white gray in the eyes of a designer.
The cracked screen
may have color differences and unevenness.
As a professional design display,
first of all,
there must be strict selection standards.
Mingji BenQ PD2705U
uses a variety of strict testing.
Choose a panel with color stability and efficiency
and is equipped with Mingji's unique AQColor color adjustment.
Ensure that each display comes out
in accordance with industry color standards.
Let designers no longer worry about color differences.
The color is uneven and uneven.
It often creates a work-to-work connection for designers,
which brings great challenges and difficulties.
How does the color look?
It's all different.
Mingji PD2705U
makes the screen evenly controlled,
adjusts the area of more than 25 pieces of the screen separately,
reduces the difference in each color and brightness,
makes it colorless
and ensures the accuracy and consistency of the image display.
It is also the first professional design display
that has been certified by Penton in the current market.
A common misunderstanding is that
the display should be brighter and better.
However, when displaying SD20,
turning on the brightness too high
means that the content of the production will be discolored.
The brightness too high can also make the eyes tired.
The correct use method is to adjust the brightness to the appropriate value
before use.
In order to satisfy the picky eyes of designers,
the appearance uses a simple cylinder-shaped frame design,
which can be easily adjusted to the screen.
The flat base gives the designer more desk space.
The external controller HOT K-POD
sends the shortcut key to the hand.
You can also use the most commonly used professional design mode
to help you grab the inspiration of the consumer.
It's hard to cut through if you've used it before.
The professional design display of PD2705U,
which is required by the designer,
starts from the perspective of the designer
to show accurate color,
which is also the consistent persistence of the BenQ PD series
of professional design.
Okay.
We just talked about the important shortcomings.
In fact,
the first problem for designers
is the color difference.
What is the color difference?
In our industry,
it is the color difference between the display,
the color of the display,
and the color of the standard color.
This is described by DotaE.
The smaller the difference,
the better.
In the industry,
we generally think that DotaE is a professional-grade display
in the field of Dota1 and Dota3,
but we have always required it to be within the field of Dota1 and Dota2.
Therefore,
the display of our system
is to ensure the accurate output of our display from the beginning.
This is what we want.
For designers,
we want to solve the most fundamental problem.
Secondly,
we have prepared four color modes for our designers.
First, the animation design mode.
It can support a brightness adjustment from 0 to 10
that is self-defined.
When the brightness is increased or decreased,
the brightness will not be too high.
This will preserve and show more layers.
At the same time,
like this one,
the second one is the color mode.
Just like the content shown in the animation,
it can divide the same screen into two areas.
Two areas on the left,
one on the left is the sRGB mode,
one on the right is the animation design mode,
and one on the right is the sRGB mode.
In this way,
you can display two effects on the same screen at the same time.
There may be a situation where
our designer is editing a video under P3
or doing something else.
At the same time,
it can display the viewing effect of our user under normal sRGB.
This is a very practical thing.
Next is the dark mode.
The dark mode is used to deal with
the environment light with a relatively low brightness.
We designed a mode
that can optimize the brightness and contrast
to improve the detail of the image in the dark environment.
You can see the contrast on the right.
There are almost no details in the dark part of the normal image.
But after opening this mode,
you can clearly see some layers and lines.
Then there is a mode that we developed
specifically for CAD and CA-M.
This mode is mainly to enhance the brightness and contrast of the lines and images.
On the left,
you can see the contrast after opening the CAD mode.
You can see the contrast after opening the CAD mode.
On the right is the normal image.
You can also see the clothes that AMD shows
on the first display in the left side of our stage.
Because you may be far away from it,
it's obvious to the viewer.
When you enter the stage,
you can see the line below.
It's very clear and sharp.
When you see these things clearly,
the fatigue of the eyes also has a slow effect.
So these are the four
modes that are designed for designers.
What else do we have next?
Our CAD-C
The CAD-C mode
has also received a patent.
What else?
We also have the MAC Look mode.
This mode is because we have considered
the daily life of our designers.
Most of the everyday devices
are Apple products.
You may need to agree
an Apple-colored device like this.
When you are choosing an external big screen,
when you are choosing an external big screen,
an Apple-colored device
will be a good source of work.
So we developed
the Apple M-Book mode.
The M-Book mode
allows your Apple products
M-Time, M-Mac,
and M-Book
to be unified with this big screen.
This is the M-Book mode
that we have brought to you.
What else?
We also have KVM,
which is a set of keys
that can control
the functions of multiple main machines.
For example,
if we use a main machine at the same time,
and then connect a laptop,
it can be connected at the same time
to a computer.
We only need a small keyboard,
which is the small keyboard in the lower right corner.
If we switch it and press it,
we can make a switch
to a different main machine.
For the rest,
we even have
for the designer's eyes,
we also have CorridorNet,
which is a smart eye mode
with four modes.
It allows everyone
to protect their eyes as much as possible.
The above is
the entire design concept
of CorridorNet.
Next,
we also invite
some teachers
from many industries
to experience our products.
For example, Sun Junqing,
a well-known color-adjusting teacher
used our display
and said that
the color requirements of our display
are relatively strict.
It is a fairly faithful
and reliable
friend of mine.
Currently,
we have nine of these models
in our entire
CorridorNet series.
They are available in different sizes
and different needs.
They are available in all variants,
including our 34-inch
large fish cake.
Some designers may have
such a need.
We have them in our entire series.
Welcome,
designers,
to experience them.
Lastly,
I would like to share
some information
that we have prepared for you.
Recently,
we have launched
a new fire system.
This new fire system
means that we want to invite
more designers
to experience
our
high-tech
activities.
This is
what we want
more teachers
to know
and to use
such good products,
such good products.
Lastly,
please pay attention
to these two,
scan these two.
One is
our assistant,
a wind turbine
with our
private design
display.
This assistant
is the one we have
specially designed
for you today.
It is a
big voucher
for our products.
After scanning,
you can
directly
access
the dialogue window.
On the right,
there is a wind turbine
with our private design
display.
We will
post
our
new fire
project
notice
or information
on it.
So,
please pay attention
to it.
Well,
my speech
ends here.
Thank you.